(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T21:49:03.132731",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
To our guests:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
桃鈴ねね 1st LIVE「おねねねねねねねね！超開花」
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Momosuzu Nene 1st LIVE "Onenenenenenene! Full Bloom"
The performance will begin shortly.
ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
To our guests:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
桃鈴ねね 1st Live 「ねねねね超会議」
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: Nenenene Chokaigi
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった！
I got hooked on anime, and now I really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
To be able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
...is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
Gアニソン宣言！ JOYSOUND
[JOYSOUND Anime Song Declaration!]
桃鈴ねね ホロプラスジャック
[Momosuzu Nene holoplus JACK]
タレントの投稿＆高音質ボイス！ ホロプラス
[Talent posts & high-quality voices! holoplus]
桃鈴ねね 1st Solo Live「花咲く＊ねねねねねねねね超開花！」
[Momosuzu Nene 1st Solo Live: Blooming* N-N-N-N-N-N-N-N Super Blooming!]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will start soon]
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Flashing lights during performance / Cheering loudly is OK]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will start soon]
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Flashing lights during performance / Cheering loudly is OK]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon...
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is OK!
桃鈴ねね 1st Live「超開花」
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: Super Blooming
Please wait a while for the performance to begin.
ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください
To all visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は、桃鈴ねね 1st Live「ねねねねねねねねっ！超開花」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Momosuzu Nene's 1st Live, "Nenenenenenenene! Super Blooming" today!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end, we have a few announcements.
お利口だね、みんな。
Good boys and girls, everyone.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は、固くお断りしております。
Taking photos, recording audio, or using recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっておりますので、喫煙はご遠慮ください。スパスパ禁止です。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue, so please refrain from smoking. No puff-puffing allowed!
そして、万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
And in the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please don't push yourself and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Acts like moshing, diving, jumping excessively, throwing objects onto the stage,
他のみなさんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止としております。
and any behavior that causes trouble for others or disrupts the show is strictly prohibited.
でも、みんなに飛んでほしいところもあるから、そこは飛ぼうね！
But there are some parts where I want everyone to jump, so let's jump there!
ルールを守って盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's follow the rules and have a blast!
そして、演出の都合上、通路にお荷物を置いたり、足を出さないようにしてください。
Also, for stage production reasons, please do not leave your belongings or stick your feet out in the aisles.
これ、とっても重要です。
This is extremely important.
もしかしたら、あのお荷物とか足がなくなっちゃう恐れがあるので、
Because your belongings or feet might disappear,
ちゃんと収納しといてください。
please make sure to store them away properly.
また、本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
In addition, cameras for video streaming and photography are present in the venue today, and the audience may be captured.
映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「#ねね超開花」です！
Also, the live show's hashtag is #NeneSuperBlooming!
トレンド1位ありがとう！
Thank you for making us trend #1!
まだまだハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてね！
Keep using the hashtag to build up the excitement!
それでは、開演までもうしばらくです。みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
Now then, it's just a little longer until the show starts. Let's pump things up together!
桃鈴ねねでした！
This was Momosuzu Nene!
ねね！ ねね！ ねね！ ねね！
Nene! Nene! Nene! Nene!
3、2、1、Go！
Three, Two, One, Go!
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走
Nenennenennenene! Great Rampage
満開
Full Bloom
桃鈴ねね 1st Live ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね！大爆走
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live
Nenennenennenene! Great Rampage
ご注文のスーパーアイドル準備中
16:30に到着予定
Your ordered Super Idol is preparing
Scheduled to arrive at 16:30
準備完了
Preparation Complete
配達中
Delivering...
東京ガーデンシアター
TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Tokyo Garden Theater
なななな ななじゃなくて
It's not Na-Na-Na-Na...
にににに ににじゃなくて
It's not Ni-Ni-Ni-Ni...
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくて
It's not Nu-Nu-Nu-Nu...
のののの ののじゃなくて
It's not No-No-No-No...
うーー、ねね！
Ooooh, Nene!
ねね！ よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Nene! Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
こんねねー！
Kon-nene!
桃鈴ねねなのです！
I'm Momosuzu Nene!
オレンジ、桃、餃子、キャロット、すべてを繋げて
Orange, peach, gyoza, carrot, connecting them all,
新星から参りました アイドル志望の最高級！
I came from a new star, an aspiring idol of the highest class!
ねねちゃーーん！
Nene-chan!
朝から晩まで行きましょう 世代を繋げて進め
Let's go from morning till night, connecting generations as we advance!
ファンもアンチも野良犬も 根っこを増やしていこう
Even fans, antis, and stray dogs, let's expand our roots!
諦めの悪さは 長所だよね
My persistence is my strong point, right?
あんなこともあったけど
Though there were times like that...
悔しいこともあったけど
...and though there were frustrating times...
大丈夫 今日も光を目指して
...it's alright, today too, heading towards the light!
いつかはきっと スーパーウルトラ
Someday, surely, Super Ultra...
スーパーハイパーねねち！
...Super Hyper Nenechi!
ついてきて！
Follow me!
限界振り切って 全開で行こう
Break past your limits and let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば 何とかなるよ
If you give it your all, everything will work out!
こうだっていい そうだっていい
This is fine, that is fine,
肩肘張らずにいこうよね
let's just relax and go!
ね！ ね！ ね！ ねっ！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne!
さいこちょー！
Feeling great!
ねね！ よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Nene! Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
ねね！ みんなも一緒に！
Nene! Everyone together!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
野菜たくさん栽培して お菓子揃えて準備して
Growing lots of vegetables, gathering sweets and preparing them,
トマト苦手 ネギも苦手
I don't like tomatoes, I don't like green onions either,
やっぱり睡眠が大事だよね
after all, sleep is the most important, right?
たったひとりの人に愛されたい？
Do I want to be loved by just one person?
ちゅっちゅ！
Chu-chu!
大好きなみんなに愛されたい！
I want to be loved by all of you whom I love!
ちゅっちゅ！
Chu-chu!
欲張りなんだ
I'm just greedy,
ハイパーねねち！
Hyper Nenechi!
限界振り切って 全開で行こう
Break past your limits and let's go at full throttle!
歌は誰にも負けたくないんだ
I don't want to lose to anyone when it comes to singing!
大きな声で 叫ぶ前に
Before shouting in a loud voice,
ちょっとトイレに行ってくるね
I'm just going to the restroom for a bit, okay?
もっとみんな声出してくれないと
If you all don't raise your voices more,
ねね、トイレから帰ってこないんだからね！
Nene won't come back from the restroom, you know!
ねね！ せーのっ！
Nene! Ready, set...
オシッコ！
Pee-pee!
なななな ななじゃなくて
It's not Na-Na-Na-Na...
にににに ににじゃなくて
It's not Ni-Ni-Ni-Ni...
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくて
It's not Nu-Nu-Nu-Nu...
のののの ののじゃなくて
It's not No-No-No-No...
みんな、ありがとうございまーーす！
Everyone, thank you so much!
限界振り切って 全開で行こう
Break past your limits and let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば 何とかなるよ
If you give it your all, everything will work out!
こうだっていい そうだっていい
This is fine, that is fine,
肩肘張らずにいこうよね
let's just relax and go!
ね！ ね！ ね！ ねっ！
Ne! Ne! Ne! Ne!
さいこちょーー！
Feeling great!
それじゃあ、次の曲です！
Alright, here is the next song!
ずっとカラカラに乾いているんだ まだまだ夏は終われない
I've been bone-dry all this time, summer can't end just yet!
みんな、次の曲も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone, let's get hyped for this next song!
わたあめみたいだねって 空見上げた放課後
After school, looking up at the sky, we said it looked like cotton candy.
僕らにもまだ「青」は 残っているかな？
I wonder if we still have some of that "youthful blue" left in us?
詰め込んだ教科書も 嫌なことも今だけ
The textbooks stuffed in my bag, and all the bad things, just for now...
忘れちゃって楽しまなくちゃ！
...I've got to forget them and just have fun!
シュワっとさ 溢れた
Fizzing and overflowing...
ラムネが教えてくれる
...the ramune soda tells us...
僕らはこの夏の
...that we are the stars...
主役だ！
...of this summer!
ずっとカラカラに乾いているんだ まだまだ夏は終われない
I've been bone-dry all this time, summer can't end just yet!
駆け足で、ほら！
Running ahead, look!
咲かせるから
Because I'll make it bloom!
だらだらうだうだもいいけど
Lazing around and complaining is fine, but...
身体がうずいてもうしょうがない！
...my body is itching to move, and I can't help it!
君と何度も
I want to draw with you...
描いてみたい続きも、さあ！
...the continuation, over and over. Come on!
覗き込んだ教室に 探したあの影も
Peering into the classroom, the shadow I searched for...
青いまま過ぎる前に なんて願ってた
...I wished for it before youth slipped away.
飲みきれなかった日々も 炭酸のよう今なら
Even the days I couldn't fully swallow down, like soda, right now...
これもアクセントって思えた
...I can think of them as just an accent.
キラッとさ 見えてたことも
Even the things that seemed to sparkle...
本当は少し濁ってて
...were actually a little cloudy...
あの頃の理想には
...and we'd probably end up...
蓋しちゃうんだ
...putting a lid on those old ideals.
みんなのペンライト、今日ここで、今、ネネでいっぱいにしてください！
Everyone, please fill this venue with Nene's colors using your penlights right now!
大人になればなるほど僕ら 心が動くことも減るのかな？
I wonder if our hearts are moved less and less as we become adults?
後戻りなんて出来やしないから 今すぐ
Since we can't turn back, right now...
ワクワクドキドキにいつだって躍らされて 朝起きちゃうような
...being swept away by excitement, waking up early in the morning...
そんな毎日でずっと！
...I want every single day to be like that forever!
きっとカラカラなままでいいんだ 鈴の音はまだ止まらない！
I'm sure staying bone-dry is fine, the sound of the bell won't stop yet!
スキップしちゃうくらい
So much that I want to skip!
弾けちゃえ！
Just let it burst!
ただただ高鳴る方へ
Just head toward where your heart beats loudest...
モヤモヤも全部飲み干せ！
...and gulp down all your worries!
君も思うまま
Keep drawing as you please...
描いていて？ずっと、ずっと
...won't you? Forever and ever.
夜に咲く火の花のように僕ら
Like fireworks blooming in the night sky...
形・色に遊びを持って たくさん咲かせてみたいの
...we want to play with shapes and colors, making so many of them bloom.
汗ばむ鼓動が
Our sweating heartbeats...
身体を追い越すの きっとそれくらいでいいの
...are outpacing our bodies, and I'm sure that's just fine.
今は何もかも脱ぎ捨てて
Right now, strip away everything...
さあ、行こう！
...and let's go!
というわけで、始まりました！
And with that, it has begun!
桃鈴ねねのファーストライブ「ねねねねねねねねねねねねのね！」超開花！
Momosuzu Nene's 1st Live: "Nenenenenenenenenenenenene no Ne!" Super Blooming!
じゃあ、まずねねの自己紹介をさせていただきたいと思います！
Now, first I'd like to do my self-introduction!
ねねが「みんなの心の」って言ったら、みんな何て返すんだっけ？
When Nene says "In everyone's hearts," what are you all supposed to reply?
その通り！よく出来ました！じゃあ行くよ！
That's right! Well done! Here we go!
ホロライブねぽらぼの「ね」、みんなの心の？
The "Ne" of hololive's NePoLaBo... in everyone's hearts...
そして桃鈴ねねー！
And Momosuzu Nene!
もう、待ちに待ちに待ったファーストライブ！
Oh, this long-awaited 1st Live!
今回のテーマは「楽しさ最大出力」をテーマに！
With this live's theme being "Maximum Joy Output"...
ねねがみんなと一緒に超開花していくっていうライブにしていきたいと思っています！
...Nene wants to make this a live where we all super bloom together!
普通のライブと違って、みんなが参加してめちゃくちゃ楽しめるようにね！
Unlike a regular live, we've set it up so everyone can participate and have tons of fun!
いっぱいワクワクとかドキドキを持ってきたから、みんな楽しみにしててね！
I've brought so much excitement and heart-throbbing moments, so look forward to it!
そしてねねのファーストアルバム「Peach-Full Story」みんな聴いてくれた？
Also, has everyone listened to Nene's 1st album, "Peach-Full Story"?
いいね。もうなんかタオルがちょっと汗ばんでる人がいるくない？
Nice! Isn't there already someone whose towel is a bit sweaty?
みんな、どの曲が好きだった？
Everyone, which song did you like?
せーの！
Ready, go!
おー、おー、おー、ちょっと待って、そっちの人、な、何、何が好き？
Oh, oh, oh... hold on, people over there, what did you like?
全部？全部？こっち、こっちの人は？
All of them? All of them? How about over here?
全部、全部か！ねえね、もう全部好きでーす！
All of them! Nene likes all of them too!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして今回はガールズバンドの生演奏でお届けしていきます！ご紹介をさせてください！
And this time, we are bringing it to you with a live girls' band! Let me introduce them!
キーボードでバンドマスターのしえりほさん！
On keyboard and our band master, Shieriho-san!
そしてギターの、三ツ丸りおさん！
And on guitar, Mitsumaru Rio-san!
かっこいい！
So cool!
そしてベースの、あみベイダーさん！
And on bass, Ami Vader-san!
渋くていいね！
Nice and groovy!
ドラムの、坂田奈々さんです！
And on drums, Sakata Nana-san!
はい！そしてちょっとね、配信の方にも触れていきたいと思うんですけど、みんなコメントいっぱいありがとう！
Yes! And I also want to address the stream audience. Thank you so much for all your comments!
この辺にね、あのー、配信の人が見ているカメラがあるの。
Right around here, we have the camera that the stream viewers are watching through.
いぇーい！
Yay!
みんなありがとう、いっぱいスクショ撮ってね！
Thank you everyone, make sure to take lots of screenshots!
そして今回のライブの感想とかはね、全部ハッシュタグ、ももす... あ、違う。
And for your thoughts on today's live, please use the hashtag Momos... Ah, wait, that's wrong.
違う、違う、違う。
No, no, no.
ハッシュタグ #ねね超開花 でたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot with the hashtag #ねね超開花!
そして今、YouTube、そしてTikTokでご覧の方は、次の曲まで聴けるので、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいなって人は、概要欄から配信サイトへGOしてください！
For those watching on YouTube or TikTok right now, you can listen until the next song. So if you want to keep pumping things up, please GO to the streaming site from the description box!
さあみんな、始まる前からギラファねね熱唱してたけど、まだまだライブ始まってたった2曲だからね！
Alright everyone, you were already singing along passionately to "Giraffa Nene" before we started, but we've only played two songs!
早速次の曲いこうかな！
Let's head straight to the next song!
次は、少ししっとりめの曲から聴いてください。
For the next one, please listen to a slightly more mellow song.
ぼやけて見えるかな
I wonder if it looks blurry...
桜色に染まった
...dyed in cherry blossom pink.
帰り道の途中
On my way back home,
流れていく春の吹雪
a spring blizzard of petals drifts by.
となりを歩いて
Walking right beside you,
少し背伸びしていた
I stretched myself a little taller.
変わらない距離を
The unchanging distance between us—
本当は縮めたくて
truth is, I wanted to close it.
見えなくて
Unable to see,
言わなくて
unable to say,
またねじゃ足りないよ
just saying "see you" isn't enough.
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we'll meet again someday.
君と
With you...
何回だって 何回だって
Time and time again,
笑い合えた春の日
those spring days we laughed together.
風に乗って ふわり 消えた
Riding the wind, they gently faded away.
それでも忘れない
But even so, I won't forget.
届けた手と手、離れていく
Our joined hands are drifting apart...
言葉を形にしていった
...as we tried to give form to our words.
甘く揺れて溶けた想い
My feelings swayed sweetly and melted away.
それでも忘れない
But even so, I won't forget.
さよならじゃなくて、ありがとう
Not saying "goodbye," but "thank you."
手を繋いで
Holding hands,
胸の奥で染まった
deep in my heart, they dyed—
あどけない気持ち
—these innocent feelings.
本当は伝えたくて
Truth is, I wanted to convey them.
届けたい
I want to reach you,
届かない
but I can't reach you.
またねじゃ足りないけど
Even though "see you" isn't enough,
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we'll meet again someday.
君と
With you...
何回だって 何回だって
Time and time again,
見上げた空の色も
even the color of the sky we looked up at.
風に乗って ひらり 飛んだ
Riding the wind, it lightly fluttered away.
それでも忘れない
But even so, I won't forget.
...花びらもいいの
...and even the petals are lovely.
これから
From now on...
描く未来図
...the future blueprint we draw...
魔法みたいに染めて
...will be colored like magic.
きっとそこに行くから
I'll surely go to that place,
明日だとしても
...even if it's tomorrow.
昨日も今も明日も 褪せない記憶
Yesterday, today, and tomorrow, memories that won't fade...
写真みたいに色付いて
...coloring vibrantly like a photograph.
ずっとずっとの思い出たち
Our eternal, everlasting memories...
春の匂いがした
...carried the scent of spring.
君と泣いたって泣いたって
Even if we cried and cried together,
笑い合えた春の日
...those spring days we shared laughter on...
風に舞って ふわり消えた
...danced in the wind and softly vanished.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I will never forget.
ほどけた手と手 離れてく
Our fingers untangled as we drifted apart,
言葉を探していた
...searching for the right words to say.
甘く触れて溶けた思い
The sweet, touching, and melting feelings...
それでも忘れない
Even so, I will never forget.
サヨナラじゃなくて
Instead of saying goodbye...
ありがとう
...thank you.
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let our brand new heartbeats resonate!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました。
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.